Oh, and Gwon Sik.
I have something to ask you.
It's about that child.
Do you happen to know what happened to him?
What child?
The child from 25 years ago.
The one who survived the accident.
Why do you ask about that child?
I suddenly got curious.
How would I know that?
I was sent straight to prison back then,
and I was not out in the world for five years.
Last time, I asked you if Team Leader Ko...
was the son of someone the Chairman knew.
But it turns out Team Leader Ko's father...
was the head of design at Gangsu Construction.
You really did not know?
His photo was in the video at the Chairman's living funeral.
Sung Jun.
Look at this. There they go again.
How is it that the moment I walk in, the conversation just stops?
What brings you to the secretary's office?
Well, I have something to discuss
with Chief Secretary Seo for a moment.
Secretary Jo, I am sorry, but can you go to the first-floor cafe...
and get that drink I ordered last time?
The Iced Salted Caramel Hazelnut Mascarpone...
In that case,
I will step out for a moment.
Okay. Thank you.
Wow. I guess it is because he is so smart.
He is quick on the uptake too.
Go ahead. What is it you have to say to me?
On the day of my father's living funeral,
Gyeol was on a call,
and I saw his expression suddenly change.
What was Gyeol's call about?
What's with you? Why are you not answering my question?
It was a call...
from the Jeongbin Police Station Traffic Investigation Unit.
Jeongbin Police Station?
Why would they call Gyeol?
Gyeol was looking for his father's case file.
Why's he looking into something from 25 years ago now?
I wonder.
He probably wants to know the truth.
Goodness.
So, what are you going to do?
What do you mean by that?
Well, if he digs into the case file,
he is going to find out that you are the one...
who killed his father.
- Gyeol trusted and relied on you? - Sir!
Why? What?
What? Am I wrong?
It is true, is it not? You are the culprit.
But it is not like it will be easy for him to find out.
So much time has passed. I doubt any information is left.
Do not worry. It is fine.
What do you think will happen if Gyeol finds out?
- What? - The truth will out.
I believe that is what you told me last time.
Look, I know you must think I'm a nobody.
I heard she was adopted overseas. To France or someplace, right?
Gwon Sik, secrets don't stay secret forever.
However hard you try to hide it, the truth comes out eventually.
You...
You know the saying about an awl in a pocket?
Then you can see for yourself when that happens.
When the awl finally pokes through the pocket.
What does that mean?
Why are you saying that to me?
Yes, Chairman.
I will see you later.
Yes.
What? Is my father calling for you?
If you have nothing more to say, please leave.
Hey. This is my company. Who are you to tell me to leave?
I am warning you again.
Don't do anything reckless.
Understand?
What? "An awl in a pocket?"
You need to get stabbed by that awl in your own pocket...
to knock some sense into you.
Yes, Father.
This is the file with the project budget summary...
for each candidate site.
Please review it to see if the budget execution is feasible.
All right, just leave it there. I'll look over it later.
Yes, sir.
But what's wrong? Did something bad happen?
Hey.
Tell Team Leader Ko to come to my office.
Right now.
Team Leader Ko took a half-day off. He's not here.
What? A half-day?
With the third competition coming up,
what on earth is he doing taking a half-day off?
Actually, Gyeol has been...
looking for the case file on his biological father's death.
What? Does he think this company is a joke?
The competition is right around the corner,
and he's taking time off for personal matters?
Why are you so upset?
But Gyeol is working hard to prepare for the competition.
Then why is someone so dedicated...
so obsessed with something from 25 years ago?
Tell him to get back to the office now. Immediately!
It says the case file is still on record.
Please fill out the application to view and copy the records.
Okay, I will.
The prosecutor in charge will review your application
to decide if access will be granted,
so you may not be able to see the files even after applying.
- Okay. - The review takes 2 to 3 weeks.
Father.
Will I finally find out this time?
What happened that day?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I can't remember anything.
Yes, General Director Ko.
What? President Ko?
(View Now)
(Seoul Citizen Daily)
(May 16, 2001, 10:40pm Car Rear-End Collision, Jeongbin-Gu)
I found it!
What? What did you find?
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm sorry.
Don't you think something's going on...
with Team Leader Ko and Jo Eun Ae lately?
Now that you mention it.
Well, I'm not sure about Eun Ae,
but Team Leader Ko has seemed pretty down lately.
It's not like they can be happy all the time.
What do you mean by that?
What? Oh, it's nothing.
Han Ji Hun, are you jealous?
What?
- Jealous? - Whenever they come up,
you get a little cynical.
It's almost like you hope things don't work out between them.
When have I ever done that?
Hey, don't go accusing an innocent person.
Team Leader Ko, where are you? I think I found it.
I searched all the major daily papers, and nothing came up
so I fed the information to Joy, and it just popped up now.
It's a short article from a local paper,
so hurry back.
- Jo Eun Ae. - Yes.
Do you have a moment?
Yes, of course.
(Conference Room)
After attending the living funeral, I started thinking.
If I were to hold my own funeral, who would I invite?
Who would I want to hold hands with one last time...
and share one last meal with?
My family.
And after them, I thought of Team Leader Ko.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm just saying that Team Leader Ko is like family to me.
I won't.
I completely understand what you mean.
I heard from General Director Ko that...
Team Leader Ko is looking for old accident records?
You heard about that?
Team Leader Ko wants to recover his lost memories.
I thought I heard you say you had found something.
I did.
The local police station didn't have any records of the accident,
so Team Leader Ko went to the prosecutor's office to check.
But I think I just found the article about the accident.
You did?
I can't imagine it was easy finding records for an accident that old.
Yes, I finally found it,
but I'm not sure how helpful it'll be.
Team Leader Ko...
His birthday is the same day as his father's death anniversary,
so he's never celebrated it.
He hasn't been able to open up to anyone,
and he's lived a lonely life.
It must have been because of that trauma.
Yes, I had a feeling.
You're the one who managed to open Team Leader Ko's heart...
when no one else could, so I'm sure you'll do fine.
But I really hope that this time,
he can get his lost memories back...
and overcome his pain.
Yes, that's what we're hoping for.
And if you need my help, please let me know.
Yes, Ms. Seo.
You didn't have to pack me a lunch today.
Why? You said you didn't like eating out.
We're on an alternating lunch schedule.
An alter-what?
Alternating. I take the even days.
Anyway, today is Bung Woo's...
No, it's the day Writer Seo packs lunch.
So you two are using work as an excuse to hang out?
Mom, I've been following my curfew perfectly these days,
so no nagging.
The webtoon we worked on together will be released in a week.
How is it? Think it'll do well?
Of course. Look who wrote it and who drew it.
Is he any good? He seems a bit flaky.
What are you talking about?
Mom, no one understands my story better than Bung Woo.
We're going to be a huge success.
Okay, then. Make it a huge hit.
And since I already packed this, take it and eat it.
- Okay. - Okay.
- I'm leaving. - Okay, don't forget your curfew.
Yes, Mom.
Lunch?
No, I don't think I'll go today.
I have a lot to do at home,
and I should be considerate of Min Ho's mom.
Why Min Ho's mom?
Why are you walking on eggshells around her?
I'm not walking on eggshells.
But from Min Ho's mom's perspective,
an unexpected sister-in-law showing up must be stressful.
Yes, let's have lunch at my place next time.
Okay.
Are the lunches packed? Let's see.
Is that all?
Who is this tiny portion supposed to feed?
What do you mean, tiny? It's a perfect single serving.
That's my point. Why is it only for one person?
You could have packed more when you were making it.
Do it again. Pack some more for me.
You little brat. Did you think I wouldn't know?
You're always asking for huge lunches.
You've been giving them all to that girl, haven't you?
Giving them to her? What are you talking about?
Bung Nim always packs a big lunch for two anyway.
I told you. She's not the one for you.
A softie like you...
should never be with a strong-willed girl like her.
A woman should be sweet, kind, and gentle like me.
No way.
You, gentle?
Whatever. Anyway, next time you pack my lunch...
What are they called again?
Right. Make me some bibi rolls.
- What? Bibi rolls? - You know the ones.
The ones with bibimbap on a wheat crepe that you roll up.
They're so delicious.
Get out of here before I decide to roll you up instead.
And you call yourself gentle?
Terrifying is more like it. Goodness.
I'm heading out.
I swear.
(Confirm Chairman's Breakfast Schedule)
(Jeongbin Police Station, Traffic Investigation Unit Number)
What's this?
"Request for a traffic accident report."
"2001?"
What traffic accident was that?
After the business went bankrupt,
he was at the Gangsu Construction overseas branch.
Is this another one of the Chairman's background checks?
Honestly.
Eun Ae made this?
She takes such good care of her boyfriend,
even though she's all thumbs.
Goodness. The son...
and father are spitting images of each other.
No wonder he looked familiar.
Why did you have to leave so soon and make your son so lonely?
Don't you worry. All of us...
will make sure he's not lonely.
That day,
you couldn't really enjoy yourself because of me, could you?
Not at all. Everyone was having a blast.
I was very worried,
but you're playing janggi with me again,
and I'm so relieved, Chairman.
You looked really close with that owner of the pancake restaurant.
It's very nice to see.
Pardon? You mean her?
I wasn't sure at first, but we have great conversations.
It feels like I've made a good friend in my old age.
I'm glad you've made a good friend.
The most important things when you get older...
are your health and your friends.
Yes. If only we'd had a little more time yesterday...
We were going to perform a line dance for you.
It's a shame we couldn't show you.
Then I'll arrange a time, so you can show me.
Really? Should we?
Checkmate.
Darn it, you caught me off guard.
Are you finished?
I made acorn jelly soup for lunch. Please come in.
Acorn jelly soup? Sounds great.
Thanks to Madam,
looks like we're having genuine acorn jelly soup today.
You go on ahead. I'll clean up and come in.
Goodness.
Hello. How are you, sir?
- Very well. Thank you very much. - Hey...
Madam made some acorn jelly soup.
- Would you join us for a bowl? - What did you say?
Join us for some acorn jelly soup.
Acorn jelly soup.
Listen,
I've tolerated you until now...
since you've lived longer in this house,
and you're the old-timer,
- but I can't take it anymore. - What? Can't take what?
What did you just say to me?
That you're going to make me into acorn jelly soup?
Just because my husband is easy-going...
and calls you by a friendly title,
you think you can get away with anything, don't you?
Good grief. When did I say I'd make you into acorn jelly soup?
I said the Madam made some and that you should have a bowl.
What?
- So I didn't hear you correctly? - Give me a break. Honestly.
I'm not eating it.
The name is so unpleasant, so I've lost my appetite.
Seriously. What kind of a name is that?
Fine, whatever.
Gosh, one of these days, that man and I...
are going to have a proper showdown.
Oh, Father. Are you eating acorn jelly soup?
Yes. You should come have a bowl, too.
No, thank you. I'm fine.
It's so savoury and rich.
The broth is just perfect.
It's the cold noodle broth Yeon Soon brought over last time.
I froze it and used it for this.
Yeon Soon's cooking is just like yours.
Yes. Her looks, her kindness, her cooking skills...
There's really not a single thing to dislike about her.
I agree.
She and her husband are both so upright and thoughtful.
They're the real deal.
Oh, my. Yeon Soon's ears must be burning right now.
Aren't you a little upset about Yeon Soon?
That you couldn't register her as your daughter.
I wouldn't say upset.
It's more of a great shame.
But I know why she refused.
What?
She refused to be recognised...
as the Chairman of Gangsu Group's daughter?
That's right.
She knows Gyeol and Eun Ae are in love with each other.
And that putting her name on the registry would hurt them.
Oh, my goodness.
That couldn't have been an easy decision to make.
Excuse me, mister,
but what if she hadn't made that decision?
If she were on the registry, they'd legally be first cousins.
Well, regardless of the paperwork, they aren't related by blood.
Why not try persuading her again?
- Mister! - Goodness.
Why don't you just eat your acorn jelly soup...
and stay out of our family's business?
That's enough.
How dare you speak to an elder that way?
Apologise.
He should know when to stop. Meddling in our family's business.
I said...
I'm sorry, mister.
Right. Since I'm the older one here,
I suppose I have to be the bigger person.
I'll be going now.
Oh, dear. When will she ever let go of her greed?
Unbelievable.
Honey, listen.
That Yong Man gets my blood pressure so high,
I can barely stand it.
(President Ko Dae Chi)
What's wrong now?
Who does that man think he is?
He finds fault with everything I do. I can't stand it anymore.
Fire Yong Man right now.
Crystal.
Your husband isn't exactly at leisure,
and he's not in the mood for your complaining.
- So let's hang up. - Honey,
this isn't me whining. Right now, in front of Father,
Yong Man says it won't be a problem for Gyeol and Eun Ae...
if Kang Yeon Ja is put on the family register,
and he said to convince Kang Yeon Ja again.
That's what's happening.
What? That guy, seriously.
All right. I'll leave work early and talk to Yong Man.
Now hang up.
Honey!
Darn it. Unbelievable.
Yes.
You wanted to see me?
Sit down.
Yes.
(Gangsu Construction)
What's with your work ethic lately?
Excuse me?
Since last week, you've been constantly...
taking half-days and coming in late.
What's that all about?
I am merely using the vacation days, which I am legally entitled to.
What? Legally entitled?
Do you think you can just take all your vacation days...
whenever you want?
Of course, for a regular employee,
there's nothing wrong with using their vacation time.
But you are different.
You're not just any employee.
You're Gangsu Group's future chairman and my son.
Father,
if you would please point out exactly what I did wrong...
You.
How much time is left until the third competition?
Just two months.
Do you really think you can prepare for it properly?
Yes, I am doing my best to prepare for the competition.
That's what you think. Is this company a joke to you?
The Retirement Community project that Grandfather gave you...
as a mission for the succession...
is a project that will secure this company's next 100 years.
- Do you get it? - Yes, I'm fully aware of that.
Then why does someone who's aware of that...
keep taking half-days off for personal business?
Your team.
Have you finished selecting the candidate sites?
Yes, we're considering it from all angles.
Considering? While taking off two or three times a week?
You call that considering?
From now on, no more personal leave.
This is...
an order from me as your father and the president.
Understand?
Understood.
I will do my best not to take time off...
during work hours from now on.
And...
I will approve of your relationship with the intern, Jo Eun Ae.
Excuse me?
It's not that I was against you two from the start.
But lately, we were discussing adding...
Jo Eun Ae's mother to our family register.
If that happened, you two would become cousins on paper.
That's why I was against it.
But Kang Yeon Ja has decided to give up on it.
She won't be added to our family register.
What?
I suppose it means she doesn't want to be an obstacle for you two.
For a mother and daughter who just met after 50 years,
it couldn't have been an easy decision.
Yes.
By the way, where were you today?
I just came from the prosecutor's office.
The pro...
The prosecutor's office?
What were you doing there?
I'm sorry, but it's not work-related.
Please excuse me.
(Gangsu Construction)
Seriously.
What is that kid thinking?
He lived quietly for 25 years. He should've just kept it that way.
(Strategic Planning Division)
Looks like everyone from Team One has gone home.
I'm sorry. The meeting ran late because of me.
Oh, not at all.
You were on leave, yet you came back in the afternoon for a meeting.
Thank you, Kim Sung Guk.
I appreciate your always-perfect data support.
Not at all. I was just doing my job.
Well, I'll be heading home now.
- Goodbye, Mr. Kim. - Good night.
So, how did your errand go?
I couldn't ask because of the meeting we had right away.
Luckily, the prosecutor's office still had the files,
so I submitted a request to view them.
But that doesn't mean I'll be able to see everything.
They said depending on their review, I might not get access.
And it'll take two or three weeks to get the results.
What? That long?
Oh, and what was that article you said you found earlier?
Oh, yes. The article about the car accident...
on May 16, 2001.
I couldn't find it no matter how hard I looked,
but this is a news brief I found using Joy.
Have you figured out the exact flow of funds yet?
Yes, it's going to take some more time.
The account in Switzerland isn't easily accessible.
But why...
Are you all right, Chairman?
I have to be. What choice do I have?
It's not like I just found out.
I don't know what I'm going to do...
If it were up to me, I'd deal with President Ko right now.
Chairman, now is not the time to expose this.
What are you talking about?
I don't have time to finish this.
That's all the more reason you must wait.
With what we know about the money trail now,
it's not enough to fix everything.
I will find something big soon and report back to you.
Did...
something happen at my funeral?
Pardon?
Oh, no. Nothing happened.
Then why did you just leave? That's not like you, Chief Seo.
I'm sorry, Chairman.
I wasn't feeling well that day.
Yes, Chief Financial Officer.
What? Seo Gwon Sik is investigating me?
- What? - For the time being,
lay low for a while.
I'm hanging up.
Seo Gwon Sik.
What is your problem?
What are you, some kind of mole?
Now that you're done with the mother-daughter search,
you're investigating me?
What makes you so high and mighty?
You're a murderer.
What?
Am I wrong?
I'm right, aren't I?
You're the murderer who killed Han Su Cheol.
(Our Happy Days)
I never should have gone to you 25 years ago.
If only I hadn't gone to see you then.
If you two hadn't shown up 25 years ago...
I saw a strange memo.
It mentioned a car accident in 2001 or something.
If it's 2001? Could it be...
Nothing happened between us.
We just fell asleep at the desk, that's all.
- What did you say? Get over here. - Stop!
I like Bung Woo.
Bung Nim.